[Music]
thank you for calling united care this
is celine how nice is you today hi my
name is cassandra vidique
i'm a colleague from michigan medical
center and i'm checking on a client
status
sure i can assist you to check on the
client status by the way let me have
your best callback number just in case
the line get disconnected
sure my callback number is 734-976-5220
thank you and you may also have your
provider mba number
okay
my provider npa number is
is going to be
231-377-1113
all right thank you for verifying the
provider information now i may have the
member id
sure
member id is h is in handrail then the
number is 5461560
thank you and can you please verify the
patient name and date birth
okay patient name is orlando west
until birth is january 22nd of 1948.
thank you let me just verify this
patient information okay
bear with me
yeah sure take your time
all right i already have the patient
information with me
you've mentioned that you want to check
on the client status
yes i'm checking on the client status
for date of service of january 1st 2022
okay may know the bill the amount on
this claim
build amount is one thousand dollars
even
okay
let me go ahead and check the claim
status for you
your problem
just take your time
thank you
all right uh cassandra is object
this claim was denied as no
authorization on file
okay
so kenny got the claim received date and
the denial tape
sure claim received on january 2nd of
and it was denied on january the 15th of
okay
thank you
uh
let me check if i have the odd number in
my system
okay
all right
i have the odd number can you check if
this odd number is valid for my date of
service or not
sure
what's the authorization number
okay
odd number is 143
thank you
well
i'm saying that this authorization is
invalid for date of service
okay
so can we obtain a retro authorization
for this claim
no i'm sorry
we do not provide retroauthorization
okay so can we appeal on this plane
yes
you have 120 days from denial day to set
an appeal for this claim
okay so in that case can i get the
appeals mailing address
yeah sure
you ready
yup
appeals mailing edges is po box
one three two
zero two
atlanta georgia
po box 13202
atlanta georgia 503 2l
okay thank you and we have the call
reference number
sure
call reference number is one
dash
one for three
six nine two
okay
thanks for help julian that's all i need
have a nice day bye
thank you for calling united care have a
good one bye
[Music]